Herold J. Wiens Collection
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress
- [China] by United States. Air Force.,., 60; Photo Index; 1:15,000; Format: Aerial Index only; Index only.; "Sortie 21PS M-8/28. Height 31,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "
- [China] by United States. Air Force.,., 61; Photo Index; 1:12,500; Format: Aerial Index only; Index only.; "Sortie 3-9FS/76. Height 25,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "
- [China] by United States. Air Force.,., 62; Photo Index; 1:14,500; Format: Aerial Index only; Index only.; "Sortie 21PS/M9-3-B. Height 28,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "
- [Ailinginae Island, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 63; 8 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "North 11o 8' East 166o 24' "
  Marshall Islands
  Ailinginae Island, Kwajalein Islands
- [Maloelab Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 64; 1 Aerial Photograph; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie MI 24." Height Unknown.; "North 8o 45' East 171o 3' "
  Maloelap Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Namorik Islet, Namorik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 65; 7 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 45." Height Unknown.; "North 5o 36' East 168o 7' "
  Marshall Islands.
  Namorik Atoll
- [Likiep Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 66; 2 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 45." Height Unknown.; "North 9o 53' East 169o 9' "
  Likiep Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Gardner Atoll, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force., 67; 1 Aerial Photograph; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 4o 40' West 174o 32' "
  Kiribati.
  Nikumaroro Islands
- [Ailuk Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 68; 6 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 32-24."
  Ailuk Atoll
- [Utirik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 69; 5 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 32-24."
  Utirik Atoll
- [Likiep Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 70; 12 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 32-24." Height Unknown.; .
  Likiep Atoll
- [Hull Island, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force.,., 71; 4 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 4o 30' West 172o 5' "
  Hull Island, Phoenix Islands
- [Enderbury Island, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force.,., 72; 8 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 3o 3' West 171o 3' "
- [Gardner Island, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force.,., 73; 5 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 3o 38' West 171o 35' "
  Gardner Island, Phoenix Islands
- [Kili, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 74; 5 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 47." Height Unknown.; "North 5o 39' East 169o 4' "
  Kili, Kwajalein Islands
- [Wotje Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 75; 29 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie MI 47." Height Unknown.; "North 9o 27' East 170o 2' "
  Wotje Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Rongerik, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 76; 4 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie MI 64." Height Unknown.; "North 11o 21' East 167o 26' "
  Rongerik Atoll,Kwajalein Islands
- [Arno Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 77; 9 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 59." Height Unknown.; "North 7o 5' East 171o 41' "
  Arno Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 78; 13 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 62." Height Unknown.; "North 7o 9' East 171o 12' "
  Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Ailuk Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 79; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 61." Height Unknown.; "North 10o 20' East 169o 56' "
  Ailuk Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Ujelang Islet, Ujelang Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 80; 11 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 48." Height Unknown.
  Ujelang Atoll
- [Calalin Islet, Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 81; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 50." Height Unknown.
- [Utirik & Pigawak Islets, Utirik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 82; 5 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 45." Height Unknown.
  Utirik & Pigawak Islets, Utirik Atoll
- [Ebon Islet, Ebon Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 83; 13 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 7." Height Unknown.
  Ebon Islets, Ebon Atoll
- [Kejien & Lukunor Islet, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 84; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 13."Height Unknown.
  Kejien Islet, Likiep Atoll
- [Matamat Islet, Namorik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 85; 2 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 9." Height Unknown.
  Matamat Islet, Namorik Atoll
- [Ujelang Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 86; 14 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 8." Height Unknown.
- [Namu Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 87; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 20." Height Unknown.
  Namu Island
- [Pikareji(Bikaridj) Islet, Arno Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 88; 2 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 26 ". Height Unknown.
  Arno Atoll
- [Enalik, Mili, Rigeeshi Islets, Mili Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 89; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 27." Height Unknown.
  Mili Atoll
- [Meijit(Mejit) Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 90; 15 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 36." Height Unknown.
  Mejit Island
- [Wotja Islet, Ailinglapalap Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 91; 2 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 36." Height Unknown.
  Ailinglaplap Atoll
- [Various Islets & Namu Atolll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 92; 13 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 36." Height Unknown.
  Namu Atoll
- [Jaluit Island,Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 93; 6 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 37." Heigth Unknown.
  Jaluit Lagoon
- [Rongelap Atoll(Bigini), Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 94; 13 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 40." Height Unknown.
  Rongelap
- [Mili, Arno, Ratak Atolls, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 95; 2 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 43." Height Unknown.
  Ratak Atolls
- [Kili, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 96; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 47." Height Unknown.
  Kili Atoll
- [Jemo Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 97; 6 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 65." Height Unknown.
  Jemo Island
- [Majuro Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 98; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 23." Height Unknown.
- [Rongerik Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 99; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.
  Rongerik Island
- [Rongerik Atoll, Rongerik Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 100; 1 Aerial Photograph; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.
- [Taongi Atoll,Taongi Island, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 101; 16 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.
  Taongi Island
- [Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 102; 5 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 1." Height Unknown.; .
  Kwajalein Islands
- [Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 103; 4 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 31." Height Unknown.; .
- [Rongerik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 104; 5 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 33." Height Unknown.; .
  Rongerik Atoll
- [Island not Identified] by United States. Air Force.,., 105; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 46." Height Unknown.; .
  Island not Identified.
- [Island not Identified] by United States. Air Force.,., 106; 4 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 44." Height Unknown.; .
- [Ujelang Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 107; 4 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 38." Height Unknown.; .
- [Island not Identified] by United States. Air Force.,., 108; 2 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 39." Height Unknown.; .
- [Wotje Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 109; 3 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given; "North 9o 27' East 170o 14' "
  Wotje Islands
- [Eniwetok Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.., 110; 1 Aerial Photograph; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given
  Eniwetok Atoll
- [Puluwat Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 111; 1 Aerial Photograph; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given
  Caroline Islands.
  Puluwat Islands
- [Woleai Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force.,., 112; 1 Aerial Photograph; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given; .
  Woleai Isalnds
- [Areas not Identified] by United States. Air Force.., 113; 4 Aerial Photographs; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given
  Island not identified
- Manchuria., 114; 1 Map; 1:6,300,000; Format: Map
  Manchuria
  Korea, Japan
- Manchuria., 115; 1 Map; 1:6,300,000; Format: Map
- Yawata & Kagoshima, Japan by United States. Army Map Services.,., 116; 1 Map; 1:250,000; Format: Map; Multiple maps attached.; Under direction of Chief of Engineers, AMGD
  Japan
- Korea by United States. Army Map Services.,., 117; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. L302; Series sheets: Sheet 4. 4th Edition; Under direction of Chief of Engineers, AMGD
  Korea
- Southern Japan by United States. Army Map Services.,., 118; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Mercator; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. L302; Series sheets: Sheet 3. 4th Edition; Under direction of Chief of Engineers, AMGD
- Japan by United States. Army Map Services.,., 119; 1 Map; 1:2,000,000; Azimuthal Equidistant; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5204; Series sheets: 1st Edition
- Yellow Sea Northern Portion by O.N.I. & M.I.D. War Department.,., 120; 1 Map; 1:500,000; Format: Map; No. 30 Yellow Sea Northern Portion.; Japanese Naval Air Chart. Chief of Engineers: U.S.A.
- Nagoya by United States. Army Map Services.,., 121; 1 Map in 2 parts; 1:250,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5303; Series sheets: Sheet 19 and 20. 1st Edition; Japan Road Map. Under direction of Chief of Engineers,GDAM
- Asia 1:1,500,000. Ch'eng-tu by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 122; 1 Map; 1:1,500,000; Gauss Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5304; Series sheets: Sheet X-12, "Ch'eng-tu", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from a USSR map dated 1940.
- Asia 1:1,500,000. Hankow by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 123; 1 Map; 1:1,500,000; Gauss Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5304; Series sheets: Sheet X-13, " Hankow", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from a USSR map dated 1940.
- Asia 1:1,500,000. Peip'ing by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 124; 1 Map; 1:1,500,000; Gauss Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5304; Series sheets: Sheet IX-13, "Peip'ing", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from a USSR map dated 1941.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Chungking by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 125; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet N H-48, "Chunking", 1st Edition-AMS 3; Copied from Survey of India dated 1942.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Canton by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 126; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NF 49, "Canton", 1st Edition-AMS 3; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Changsha by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 127; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; International Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet N.H-49, "Changsha", 1st Edition-AMS 4; Copied from Survey of India dated 1944.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Nanking by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 128; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NI 50, "Nanking", 1st Edition-AMS 4; Copied from Survey of India dated 1941.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Fuchou by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 129; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NG 50, "Fuchou", 5th Edition-AMS 6; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Hong Kong by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 130; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NF 50, "Hong Kong", 5th Edition-AMS 5; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Hankow by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 131; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NH 50, "Hankow", 3rd Edition-AMS 4; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Mukden by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 132; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NK 51, "Mukden", 1st Edition-AMS 1; Copied from Japanese Inperial Land Survey dated 1936.
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Shanghai by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 133; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NK 51, "Shanghai", 3rd Edition-AMS 4; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.
- Takla Makan Desert ONC-G-7 by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center.:,., 134; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map
  China,
  Kashmir
- World Aeronautical Chart. Tung-t'ing Lake by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center.:,., 135; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 494.
  Tung-t'ing Lake
- World Aeronautical Chart. Hung-tse Lake by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center.:,., 136; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 386.
  Hung-tse Lake
- World Aeronautical Chart. Hang-chou Bay by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center.:,., 137; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 492.
  Hang-chou Bay
- World Aeronautical Chart. Wei River by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center.:,., 138; 1 Map; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 384.
  Wei River
- China Physical by Haack H. Geographisch-Kartographische Anstalt, VEB, Gotha.:,., 139; 1 Map; 1:3,000,000; Format: Map; Relief shown by gradient tints and shading.; Wall Map.
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Chieh-yang by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 140; 1 Map; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Chieh-yang",Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photograpy,Central Land Survey 1937.
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Hsia-men by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 141; 1 Map; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Hsia-men", Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photograpy,Central Land Survey 1937.
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Yung-chia by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 142; 1 Map; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Yung-chia", Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Fu-chou and Nan-tai by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 143; 1 Map; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Fu-chou" and "Nan-t'ai", Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.
- Eastern China 1:50,000. Peking by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 144; 1 Map; 1:50,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. GSGS; Series sheets: Sheet 16/2,200, "Peking", 3rd Edition-AMS 3; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.
- China 1:25,000. Hankow by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 145; 1 Map; 1:25,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. L1901; Series sheets: "Hankow", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.
- China Special Strategic Map. [Southeastern China] by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 146; 1 Map; 1:4,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5207; Series sheets: "China", 3rd Edition,-AMS 3; Copied from Earlier AMS Editions.
- Hong Kong and New Territory 1:80,000. by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 147; 1 Map; 1: 80,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: GSGS 1938; Series sheets: "Hong Kong and New Territory", 2nd Edition-AMS 3; Copied from Earlier AMS Editions.
  Hong Kong
- Outline Map 1:19,000,000. [China, Japan, Pacific Ocean, Australia] by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 148; 1 Map; 1:19,000,000; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 1101; Series sheets: "Outline Map", Sheet No. 3; Copied from 1933 Municipal Plan.
- Plan of Shanghai (Sheet 1) 1:15,840. by United States. Army Map Services.:,., 149; 1 Map; 1:15,840; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: GSGS 3956
- China Transportation 1:2,750,000. by United States Foreign Economic Administration.,., 150; 1 Map; 1:2,750,000; Format: Map; Map series: N0. 1379
- China, Seen From the Direction of Guam by From Magazine [unknown]., 151; 1 Map; Format: Map
- Jan Jan's Map of Kowloon by Jan Jan Publishing Company, China.,., 152; 1 Map; 1:11,670; Format: Map; Also contains area maps and indexes.
- [South & Central China Provinces][Translated from Chinese] by [East Atlas Society][Translated from Chinese].,., 153; 1:3,200,000; Format: Map; First Printing, October 1938.; 3 Insets: "Pearl Delta Region, "Islands of the South China Sea" & "Communication Map of China and South Asia".; .
- [Administrative Map of the People's Republic of China][Translated from Chinese] by [New China Map and Atlas Society] [Translatedfrom Chinese].:,., 154; 1:4,000,000; Format: Map; First Printing. Coverage illustrates Situation as of November 1953.; Inset; "South China Islands".
- Asia and Adjacent Areas by The National Geographical Society.:,., 155; 1:9,000,000; Two Point Equidistant; Format: Map; Gilbert Grosvenor, Editor.
  Asia
- China by The National Geographical Society.:,., 156; 1:7,000,000; Albers Conical Equal-Area; Format: Map; Gilbert Grosvenor, Editor.
- Postal Map of Western Szechwan District by General Bureau of Postal Service.:,., 157; 1:500,000; Format: Map; Insets of Northern Szechwan District, Postal Stations of Sikang Province.
- People's Republic of China by Map and Atlas Publishing Society [Translated from Chinese].:,., 158; 1:9,000,000; Format: Map; Insets of Islands of South China Sea, China's Neighbors.; Includes some Japanese place names.
- People's Republic of China by Cartographers Jin Ju'an, Chen Zhifang, Yang Boru.:,., 159; 1:6,000,000; Lambert; Format: Map; Series sheets: 12th edition; Insets of Islands of South China Sea, Relief Map of P.R.C.; Inset of Administrative Districts of P.R.C.
- China and [Surrounding Countries & South East Asia} by Cartographers Jin Ju'an, Chen Zhifang, Yang Boru.:,., 160; 1:8,500,000; Format: Map; Series sheets: 1st edition; Inset of map of Korea.; List of population and areas of countries shown on map.
- The Wall Map of China by The Great China Book Company.:,., 161; 1:6,000,000; Lambert; Format: Map; Series sheets: Revised edition; Insets of Relief Map of China, Islands of South China Seas.; Inset Map of Beijing City and surrounding areas.
- Map of Taipei City by Map and Atlas Publishing Society.:,., 162; Format: Map; Tourist map of Taipei.
- Hunan Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society.:,., 163; 1:800,000; Format: Map; Insets of Changsha City, Shaoshan District. Mao's birthplace.
- Guangdong Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society.:,., 164; 1:800,000; Format: Map; Insets of Islands of South China Sea, Guangzhou City.
- Zhejiang Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society.:,., 165; 1:1,100,000; Format: Map; Inset of Hangzhou City.
- Fujian Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society.:,., 166; 1:750,000; Format: Map; Inset of Fuzhou Cit.
- Shanxi Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society.:,., 167; 1:1,100,000; Format: Map; Inset of Taiyuan City.
- Liaoning Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society.:,., 168; 1:600,000; Format: Map; Inset of Shenyang City.
- Shaanxi Province by Yechang Yasin Geography Society.:,., 169; 1:200,000; Format: Map; Insets of Xijing City, Nanzheng City.; Photocopy.
- Southeast China Costal Relief Map by Map Publishing House.:., 170; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.
- Central Yangsze Valley Relief by Map Publishing House.:., 171; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.
- Sichwan Region Relief Map by Map Publishing House.:., 172; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.
- Shanxi, Gansu, Quinghai Relief Map by Map Publishing House.:., 173; 1:1,400,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.
- Guangdong Province by Dah Chung Book Co..:., 174; 1:3,000,000; Format: Map; Insets of Hainan Island and coastal area of Guangdong Province.; In English and Chinese.
- Fujian Province Map of Fujian Province by Dah Chung Book Co..:., 175; 1:3,000,000; Format: Map; In English and Chinese.
- Map of Qing Dynasty-Daoguang 12 (1832) by Li Zhaoluo.:., 176; Format: Map; In Chinese.; Photocopy.